CONTACT

hello@isaque.me

isaque.me (Portfolio)
isaque.me/linkedin (Linkedin)

TOP SKILLS

BRAND, CREATIVE, & PD STRATEGY
PRODUCT & SERVICE IDEATION
STATS & PSYCHOMETRICS
DIGITAL DESIGN • FILMMAKING • PUBLIC SPEAKING
R • SPSS • HTML/CSS • MARKETING STRATEGY

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH (NATIVE/BILINGUAL)
PORTUGUESE (NATIVE/BILINGUAL)
SPANISH (FULL PROFICIENCY)
HUNGARIAN (ELEMENTARY)
DUTCH (ELEMENTARY)

HONORS & AWARDS

2022 GLOBAL CANNES YOUNG LIONS
PBRONZE (DIGITAL)

2022 YOUNG LIONS NL GOLD (FAIRPHONE)

2022 YOUNG LIONS NL

** SILVER (MENTELITY FOUNDATION)

2022 YOUNG LIONS NL

** HONORS (BUMA X YOUTUBE)

2021 YOUNG LIONS NL

**BRONZE (CONCERTGEBOUW)

AMSTERDAM MOBILITY CHALLENGE ★ SILVER (ADE)

FACAMP WEB GAME

**NATIONAL CHAMPION

2022 LIA CREATIVE LIAISONS MENTEE

PASSPORTS

BRAZILIAN

ITALIAN 💿

ISAQUE SENEDA

CREATIVE & PRODUCT STRATEGIST

AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS

SUMMARY

I am a strategist w/ product ideation, design, and consumer research skills. Brazilian w/ experience in 4 countries. I create products that tell stories because products are stories (Berkeley, 1713). In it to fix real problems. Fluent in behavioral sciences, psychometrics, and stats.

HOLLAND CODE

→ #「 ~~> ~@

ENTREPRENEURIAL • ARTISTIC • INVESTIGATIVE

CLIFTONSTRENGTHS

COMPETITION • SIGNIFICANCE • RESTORATIVE • COMMUNICATION • FOCUS

EXPERIENCE

PUBLICIS ITALY / LE PUB

CREATIVE & PRODUCT STRATEGIST

JUN 2021 - PRESENT (1 YEAR 6 MONTHS)

AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS

Here I joined the global Heineken team alongside top talent from the ad industry. After Data Lab, I now work at Le Garage (product/tech team) as a creative strategist using data to ideate innovation-led campaigns.

₩INEPOPPER

BRAND & PRODUCT STRATEGIST
JAN 2021 - DEC 2021 (1 YEAR)

SÃO PAULO, BRAZIL

Repositioning and rebranding of Winepopper (Brazilian gas wine opener) as a "magic kit for 40+ wine lovers". The process involved managing market research & strategy, service & product design, and media buying.

MUSEU DO AMANHÃ (MOTI)

DIGITAL DESIGNER & BRAND STRATEGIST
NOV 2018 - JUN 2021 (2 YEARS 7 MONTHS)

AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS

Traineeship where I headed the development of FORMS' global brand identity both in terms of brand strategy, as well as digital design. FORMS is collaborative platform connecting sustainability museums worldwide.

ARENAS ESPM

ART DIRECTOR & PLANNER

FEB 2016 - JUL 2016 (6 MONTHS)

SÃO PAULO BRAZTI

A student advertising agency, where I created campaigns for real Brazilian clients such as Mentos and Mondelēz Lacta BIS. The process involved collaboration with professionals from renowned agencies in São Paulo.

EDUCATION

ROTTERDAM SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT, ERASMUS UNIVERSITY

MSc, MARKETING MANAGEMENT · (2020 - 2021)

PARSONS SCHOOL OF DESIGN, THE NEW SCHOOL

STUDY ABROAD, COMMUNICATION DESIGN · (2020 - 2020)

UNIVERSITY OF AMSTERDAM

BSc, COMMUNICATION SCIENCE (*HONORS) · (2017 - 2020)
MINOR, BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION · (2018 - 2019)

ESCOLA SUPERIOR DE PROPAGANDA E MARKETING

PORTFOLIO SCHOOL, ARENAS ESPM · (2016 - 2016)

WILLEM DE KOONING ACADEMY

PROPEDEUSE, AUDIOVISUAL DESIGN · (2016 - 2017)

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

ROTARY INTERNATIONAL

YOUTH EXCHANGE STUDENT IN HUNGARY AUG 2014 - JUL 2015 (1 YEAR)

TNW CONFERENCE

STAFF

MAY 2018 - MAY 2019 (1 YEAR)

UNIVERSITY OF AMSTERDAM

MEGA TABLE, FOUNDER & STATS TUTOR
OCT 2017 - PRESENT (4 YEARS 10 MONTHS)